# TOBY TOMKINSON

### **Computer Science Graduate**

@ tobytomkinson@hotmail.co.nz

**J** 027-239-5676

Auckland, New Zealand

in toby-j-tomkinson

① ttom795

ttom795.github.io

# **TECH SKILLS**

**Programming Languages:** 

C++ C# Python JavaScript

SQL LaTeX

Web Development:

React Typescript Express.js

 $(\mathsf{MongoDB})(\mathsf{HTML})(\mathsf{CSS})$ 

Software:

Microsoft Office Nagios

Google Workspace

StarRez Property Management

Salesforce Service Cloud

Unity Engine Unreal Engine

**Operating Systems:** 

Windows OSX/MacOS

Debian Ubuntu ArchLinux

**Development Methods:** 

Agile Scrum Kanban

Waterfall Pair Programming

Continuous Integration (CI)

Continuous Delivery (CD)

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Attention to Detail Quick Learner

Adaptability | Multitasking Abilities

Planning/Organizational Abilities

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a hardworking, reliable, and motivated person with a strong computer and technology orientated background and a desire to improve myself. I have a demonstrable history of exceeding employers expectations in working practices. I have consistently sought out opportunities to expand my technical skills and tackle complex problems, and I thrive in environments where I am exposed to a variety of experiences and challenges.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Receptionist | University of Auckland

Nov 2022 - Current

Auckland, New Zealand

- Receptionist at Waiparūrū Hall
- Managed front-desk and general accommodation operations ranging from resident queries to inventory management to introduction of new processes and workflow streamlining
- Assisted in coordinating appointments and meetings for staff and residents, and prioritising tasks ensuring smooth workflow

### Teaching Assistant | University of Auckland

Mar 2022 - Current

Auckland, New Zealand

- Graduate Teaching Assistant for COMPSCI 215 and COMPSCI 315
- Provided tutoring and guidance to students
- Graded and evaluated assignments and papers, and provided constructive feedback
- Fostered a supportive learning environment and promoted active engagement through interactive teaching methods

### Research Assistant | University of Auckland

**Nov 2021 - Feb 2022** 

Auckland, New Zealand

- Worked with Dr. Ulrich Speidel
- Developed software and a novel routing algorithm for use with Low Earth Orbit satellites ( available here ) using the Unity Real-Time Development Platform

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Red Cross Comprehensive First Aid

ICDL Certified

# Research Assistant | University of Auckland

**i** Jun 2021 - Oct 2021

Auckland, New Zealand

Worked with Dr. Alex Shaw

Sales Assistant | Jaycar New Lynn

 Developed a procedural construction site for Virtual Reality-based risk assessment training for City Rail Link using the Unity Real-Time Development Platform

# **LANGUAGES**

**English: Native** 

#### iii Nov 2020 - Mar 2022

#### Auckland, New Zealand

- . 1
  - Managed clients' needs and budgets to an exceptional level
  - Developed strong company relationships through repeat customers
- Available on request

REFERENCES

### Front of House | Bodrum Kitchen, New Lynn

Feb 2018 - Jun 2020

- Auckland, New Zealand
- Took orders accurately, ensuring special requests and dietary preferences were noted
- Managed cash transactions and operated card payment systems via POS system

## **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor of Science | University of Auckland

- Feb 2019 Jun 2022
- Auckland, New Zealand
- Bachelor of Science (BSc) majoring in Computer Science

### Bachelor of Science (Honours) | University of Auckland

**i** Jul 2022 – Jun 2023

- Auckland, New Zealand
- Bachelor of Science Honours (BSc Hons) majoring in Computer Science

# PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

Low Earth Orbit Satellite Simulator | # | Unity Engine/C#

 Simulates approximate great circle routing through a LEO network between two selectable locations on Earth in real time

- A non-profit fangame based around the franchise of My Hero Academia
- Programmer, Concept Artist

#### Sea of Greed | # | Unity Engine/C#

- A pirate-adventure RPG developed as part of Gladstone Games
- Programmer, Game & Level Designer

Chippure | | Python

A Chip-8 emulator written solely using Python's default libraries

### **HOBBIES**

Baking, fantasy novels, karaoke and game development

- Showcase LEGO "Shonen Jump" Fangame
- Showcase My Hero Karting
- Showcase Shield Hero Fangame
- Showcase Mob Psycho Sentiment